{
  "level1": [
    {
      "question_id": 1,
      "question_text": "In which year did IBZ start?",
      "choice1": "2013",
      "choice2": "2019",
      "choice3": "2016",
      "choice4": "2015",
      "correct_ans": "2015",
      "level": 1
    },
    {
      "question_id": 2,
      "question_text": "The Apprentice Program connects TMU students with IBZ startups for work-related learning opportunities.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "True",
      "level": 1
    },
    {
      "question_id": 3,
      "question_text": "How long does the Lab2Market Validate program last for?",
      "choice1": "12 weeks",
      "choice2": "52 weeks",
      "choice3": "16 weeks",
      "choice4": "27 weeks",
      "correct_ans": "16 weeks",
      "level": 1
    },
    {
      "question_id": 4,
      "question_text": "You do not need to attend in-person events in Toronto to be eligible for the Raise program.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "False",
      "level": 1
    },
    {
      "question_id": 5,
      "question_text": "What does B stand for In IBZ?",
      "choice1": "Branding",
      "choice2": "Business",
      "choice3": "Boost",
      "choice4": "Build",
      "correct_ans": "Boost",
      "level": 1
    }
  ],
  "level2": [
    {
      "question_id": 6,
      "question_text": "How can you get involved with IBZ?",
      "choice1": "As a member",
      "choice2": "As an investor",
      "choice3": "As a mentor",
      "choice4": "All of the Above",
      "correct_ans": "All of the Above",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "question_id": 7,
      "question_text": "IBZ does not provide one-on-one advising and mentorship for startups",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "False",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "question_id": 8,
      "question_text": "Who can you contact to do 3D printing at IBZ?",
      "choice1": "Wesley",
      "choice2": "Harjeev",
      "choice3": "Umar",
      "choice4": "All of the above",
      "correct_ans": "All of the above",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "question_id": 9,
      "question_text": "IBZ is located at 20 Dundas St W, Toronto",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "True",
      "level": 2
    },
    {
      "question_id": 10,
      "question_text": "The Norman Esch Engineering Innovation and Entrepreneurship Awards provide financial assistance to IBZ members for startup development at various stages.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "True",
      "level": 2
    }
  ],
  "level3": [
    {
      "question_id": 11,
      "question_text": "The Innovation Boost Zone is one of the ten zones at Toronto Metropolitan University designed for collaborative projects and startup development.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "True",
      "level": 3
    },
    {
      "question_id": 12,
      "question_text": "The Centre for Engineering Innovation and Entrepreneurship (CEIE) established IBZ to educate and support entrepreneurs through the entire process from incubation to commercialization.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "True",
      "level": 3
    },
    {
      "question_id": 13,
      "question_text": "The Faculty of Engineering and Architectural Science (FEAS) is a source of talent and resources for IBZ members, contributing to innovation and societal impact",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "True",
      "level": 3
    },
    {
      "question_id": 14,
      "question_text": "IBZ focuses exclusively on technological ingenuity, without considering its social impact.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "False",
      "level": 3
    },
    {
      "question_id": 15,
      "question_text": "How many startups are currently being incubated within IBZ?",
      "choice1": "10",
      "choice2": "86",
      "choice3": "50",
      "choice4": "97",
      "correct_ans": "86",
      "level": 3
    }
  ],
  "level4": [
    {
      "question_id": 16,
      "question_text": "Which of the following is NOT an area of focus for IBZ?",
      "choice1": "Robotics",
      "choice2": "Healthtech",
      "choice3": "Energy and Cleantech",
      "choice4": "Literature and Humanities",
      "correct_ans": "Literature and Humanities",
      "level": 4
    },
    {
      "question_id": 17,
      "question_text": "What is the primary purpose of the Centre for Engineering Innovation and Entrepreneurship (CEIE) in relation to IBZ?",
      "choice1": "Offering resources and support for developing and commercializing ideas",
      "choice2": "Supporting entrepreneurs with job placements",
      "choice3": "Providing academic courses in engineering",
      "choice4": "Promoting architectural science projects",
      "correct_ans": "Offering resources and support for developing and commercializing ideas",
      "level": 4
    },
    {
      "question_id": 18,
      "question_text": "The Innovation Boost Zone (IBZ) is one of Toronto Metropolitan University's zones that provides a space for:",
      "choice1": "Political and social debates",
      "choice2": "Sports and recreational activities",
      "choice3": "Brainstorming and startup building",
      "choice4": "Music and arts performances",
      "correct_ans": "Brainstorming and startup building",
      "level": 4
    },
    {
      "question_id": 19,
      "question_text": "What type of financial assistance do IBZ members have access to through The Norman Esch Engineering Innovation and Entrepreneurship Awards?",
      "choice1": "Scholarships",
      "choice2": "Startup development funds",
      "choice3": "Research grants",
      "choice4": "None of the above",
      "correct_ans": "Startup development funds",
      "level": 4
    },
    {
      "question_id": 20,
      "question_text": "How does IBZ contribute to addressing societal challenges?",
      "choice1": "By promoting theoretical research",
      "choice2": "By focusing solely on technological advancements",
      "choice3": "By encouraging deep tech entrepreneurs with a focus on social impact",
      "choice4": "By exclusively supporting projects in the field of robotics",
      "correct_ans": "By encouraging deep tech entrepreneurs with a focus on social impact",
      "level": 4
    }
  ],
  "level5": [
    {
      "question_id": 21,
      "question_text": "The Norman Esch Engineering Innovation and Entrepreneurship Awards are only available to established startups, not to individuals with innovative ideas.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "False",
      "level": 5
    },
    {
      "question_id": 22,
      "question_text": "What is the significance of the Centre for Engineering Innovation and Entrepreneurship (CEIE) in the context of IBZ?",
      "choice1": "It offers language courses for international students",
      "choice2": "It trains students to be both engineers and entrepreneurs",
      "choice3": "It exclusively focuses on architectural science projects",
      "choice4": "It offers counseling services for students",
      "correct_ans": "It trains students to be both engineers and entrepreneurs",
      "level": 5
    },
    {
      "question_id": 23,
      "question_text": "The Innovation Boost Zone (IBZ) primarily focuses on theoretical research rather than practical implementation.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "False",
      "level": 5
    },
    {
      "question_id": 24,
      "question_text": "In addition to collaboration and kickstarting projects, what else can IBZ members do?",
      "choice1": "Participate in sports competitions",
      "choice2": "Attend cultural workshops",
      "choice3": "Develop their own art projects",
      "choice4": "Develop their own ideas or collaborate with a team",
      "correct_ans": "Develop their own ideas or collaborate with a team",
      "level": 5
    },
    {
      "question_id": 25,
      "question_text": "The Centre for Engineering Innovation and Entrepreneurship (CEIE) is exclusively for engineering students and does not support students from other disciplines.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "False",
      "level": 5
    }
  ],
  "level6": [
    {
      "question_id": 26,
      "question_text": "Which of the following is NOT mentioned as an IBZ area of focus?",
      "choice1": "Robotics",
      "choice2": "Healthtech",
      "choice3": "Music & Entertainment",
      "choice4": "Energy & Cleantech",
      "correct_ans": "Music & Entertainment",
      "level": 6
    },
    {
      "question_id": 27,
      "question_text": "The Innovation Boost Zone (IBZ) supports startups that are based on deep tech solutions and also have a positive societal impact.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "True",
      "level": 6
    },
    {
      "question_id": 28,
      "question_text": "How many areas of focus does IBZ have for startup development?",
      "choice1": "94",
      "choice2": "06",
      "choice3": "18",
      "choice4": "47",
      "correct_ans": "06",
      "level": 6
    },
    {
      "question_id": 29,
      "question_text": "The Faculty of Engineering and Architectural Science (FEAS) plays a role in driving innovation by establishing partnerships only within the academic community.",
      "choice1": "True",
      "choice2": "False",
      "correct_ans": "False",
      "level": 6
    },
    {
      "question_id": 30,
      "question_text": "What is the main goal of IBZ at Toronto Metropolitan University?",
      "choice1": "Providing scholarships to students",
      "choice2": "Hosting social events for students",
      "choice3": "Promoting artistic creativity",
      "choice4": "Fostering entrepreneurial skills and innovation.",
      "correct_ans": "Fostering entrepreneurial skills and innovation.",
      "level": 6
    }
  ]
}
